

Yury Kastsen

- +48881096343
- kastenedev@gmail.com
- Wrocław

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/kastsen

Website: https://mentalmerging.netlify.app/

Github: https://github.com/kastsen

Introduction

I help bring concepts to life, ensuring projects are launched on time. Programming, product support, and enhancement all fall within my scope of responsibilities. I hope to see the world change, so I always strive to connect my work and life with progressive projects.

My technology stack includes: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Webpack, Pixi.js, Create.js, Three.js, Gatsby.js, HTML5, Pug.js, CSS3, SCSS, Bash, Git and more.

I'm now looking forward to using my skills and experience in a fulfilling position.

Experience

12/2022 - until now

Web Games Developer

QS Games

Web Games Development and maintenance service:

- · CORAL ISLE 2 https://coralisle2.guartsoft.com/index.html
- · FARLAND https://farland.quartsoft.com/index.html
- · PAPAYA https://papaya.quartsoft.com/index.html
- · Skills: JavaScript · Typescript · Webpack · Pixi JS · Create JS · React · Redux ·

HTML5 · Git · mySQL · REST API

03/2020 - 08/2022

Playable Ads Developer

Vizor Games

Playable ads development. Framework development and support. Build automatisation. Optimization of processes and tasks, work with the team. Skills: Node.js \cdot npm \cdot Webpack \cdot JavaScript \cdot Matter JS \cdot Bash \cdot Pixi.js \cdot Spine Animations \cdot Tiled \cdot HTML5 \cdot SVN \cdot JSON \cdot ES6+

12/2019 - 03/2020

Front-end Developer

Bamboo Apps

Project support and maintenance service. Interviews, onboarding for new employees. Skills: JavaScript · Node.js · Express.js · mySQL · CSS3 · SCSS ·

SPA · UI · Github · Webpack · Git · SASS · AJAX · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) · npm · ES6+ · API · Pug.js

05/2019 - 05/2020 **Front-**

Front-end Development Speaker

School MyFreedomIT

Skills: Public Speaking · CSS3 · HTML5 · Git · Bootstrap · JavaScript

02/2018 - 11/2019

Front-end Developer

Logic Software Inc.

Work with a team, including a team of designers, developers and marketing. June training. Support and optimization of the project. Skills: Node.js \cdot JavaScript \cdot CSS3 \cdot SCSS \cdot React \cdot Web Design \cdot Agile Methodologies \cdot Scrum \cdot UX \cdot jQuery \cdot Webpack \cdot Git \cdot SASS \cdot AJAX \cdot JSX \cdot Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) \cdot JSON \cdot npm \cdot Yarn \cdot ES6+ \cdot API \cdot PHP \cdot mySQL

06/2015 - 12/2017

Web Development Specialist

inAweb

Web sites design, development and support. Building custom WordPress themes and plugins. HTML-markup, PHP, MySQL, jQuery.

05/2011 - 08/2015

Content Manager

Cultutal Daily News Portal

Content management, digital marketing, planning and implementation of audience engagement activities, generation of new ideas, community management.

Knowledge and skills

Languages:

Byelorussian (proficient) Russian (proficient) English (intermediate) Polish (pre-intermediate) Czech (pre-intermediate)

Skills:

JavaScript	HTML5	CSS3	SASS	webpad	ck noo	de.js	npm	PixiJS	WebGL
ReactJS	actJS React Native		GatsbyJS We		o Games Three.js		Project planning		
Team management Ba		Bash	MySQL	ООР	Redux	Agilo	Agile methodologies		

Education

Level of education

University

2015 - 2016

Erasmus+ EVS
Politologie

2008 - 2012

BSPU
Philology. Literature. Journalism

Certificates and trainings

2019 **School MyfreedomIT** Javascript, React JS. Front-end Development

2013 Používání vizuálních symbolů a tvůrčích přístupů

Prague

Známost s českou zkušeností v použití vizuálních symbolů a kreativních

přístupů k sociální činnosti.

Interests and hobbies

Music Nature Quad roller skating